ERIN SOVEREIGN

Product Designer · 713-829-2771

INFO



Houston, TX



Erin.Sovereign@gmail.com



☐ ErinSovereign.com



/in/erinsovereign

TOOLS

- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- InVision
- MS Office (Expert Excel certified)
- Figma
- Basic HTML
- Basic CSS
- Salesforce.com
- Miro

SKILLS

- User Research
- User Surveys & Interviews
- Competitive Analysis
- User Personas
- Information Architecture
- Wireframing
- Rapid Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- A/B Testing
- Visual Design
- Frontend Development

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Certification in UX Design | 2020

Ten month intensive UX design program focused on user-centered design principles and mastering the entire UX process from User Research to a final prototype.

Texas Christian University

Bachelor of Business Administration | 2015

PROFILE

Creative and forward-thinking UX Designer able to gain insights into user needs and translate those into actionable steps. Experience in technical customer support facilitates understanding of customer needs and provides a unique perspective on the user experience.

EXPERIENCE

Site Support Specialist II

CentralSquare Technologies | April 2018 - Feb 2020

- Provided technical and functional support to resolve complex product issues
- Coordinated efforts between end users, clients, developers, and other specialists to allow for efficient problem resolution
- Acted as a liaison for the company as an onsite support specialist dedicated to one client

Senior Product Specialist

Cvent | Feb 2017 - April 2018

- Investigated over 500 product issues reported by clients and assessed the need for changes in code at the development level
- Trained over 10 new product consultants on the Passkey product while managing their most challenging cases
- Tested integration of new client database due to company merger

Product Consultant

Cvent | Nov 2015 - Feb 2017

- Collaborated with hotel, convention bureau, and meeting planner clients to manage and troubleshoot events built in Lanyon Passkey and maintained an overall client satisfaction rating of 95%
- Wrote over 200 articles for the client-facing knowledge baseto deflect known customer issues
- Assisted the Professional Services team with operations on-site at several events with over 50,000 attendees